(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-25T22:40:14.483783",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.6-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
みんな！速報だよ！！
Everyone! Breaking news!!
なになに！？
What is it, what is it!?
一番くじ hololive DEV_IS ReGLOSSの発売が決定したんだって！！
The release of Ichiban Kuji hololive DEV_IS ReGLOSS has been confirmed!!
えーっ！！嬉しい！！
What?! That's amazing!!
ReGLOSSが一番くじ！？ドッキリか何か？
ReGLOSS is getting an Ichiban Kuji!? Is this a prank or something?
どんなラインナップなんだろ？
I wonder what the lineup is like?
みんな！運試ししてみてね！
Everyone! Be sure to try your luck!
11月13日木曜日より順次発売予定なんだって！ぜひみんな挑戦してみてね！
It's scheduled to go on sale starting Thursday, November 13! Give it a try, everyone!
なんと出来立てほやほやのサンプルをスタジオへ用意いただいております！
We even have fresh-off-the-press samples ready in the studio!
でも！ぼまえらにはまだ見せられないよ～
But! We can't show them to you guys just yet~
ちょっとだけ教えておこうかな～
Maybe I should give you a little hint~
まずは描き下ろしイラストを使ったビジュアルボードがあったよね！
First, there was a visual board featuring newly drawn illustrations, right?
イラストの背景にそれぞれにマッチしたモチーフがいろいろ入ってたよね～
Plus, the background of the illustrations had various motifs matching each member~
はじめ「押忍！」って書いてあった！
Mine had "Osu!" written on it!
ちょこのっこフィギュア！ホロライブ一番くじではお馴染みのやつもあったね
Chokonokko figures! The staple items from Hololive Ichiban Kuji were there too.
表情がとっても可愛かった！
Their expressions were super cute!
バッグに忍ばせて一緒に連れて行って欲しくない？
Wouldn't you want to slip one into your bag and take it along with you?
髪の毛の塗分けとかグラデーションとかも綺麗なんだよ～！
The hair coloring separation and gradations are so pretty too!
ラストワン賞っぽいやつは…デカかったね！
The one that looked like the Last One prize... was huge!
抱きしめて…眠れる…
You could hug it... and sleep...
ヒントは以上です！詳細は9月16日一番くじホームページで公開予定！
That's all for the hints! Details will be revealed on the Ichiban Kuji website on September 16!
お楽しみに！
Look forward to it!
お知らせはこれだけじゃない！
That's not the only announcement!
2025年9月第4週より順次発売予定！
Scheduled to release sequentially starting from the 4th week of September 2025!
ガシャポン商品
Gashapon products!
ホロライブプロダクション DEV_IS ReGLOSS
hololive production DEV_IS ReGLOSS
ミニCDコレクションが
Mini CD Collection
販売開始となりまーす！
is now on sale!
イエーイ！
Yay!
こちら小さなCDのようなチャームで
This is a small CD-like charm,
CD風プレートやジャケットカードも取り出せる仕様になってまーす！
where you can even take out the CD-style plate and jacket card!
すごーい！
Awesome!
ラインナップはデビュー曲「瞬間ハートビート」から
The lineup includes their debut song "Shunkan Heartbeat"
1st Album「ReGLOSS」など
1st Album "ReGLOSS" and more,
シークレットを含む全6種！
all 6 types including a secret!
どれが出るかはカプセルを開けてのお楽しみ〜！
Which one you get is a surprise until you open the capsule~!
ガシャポンオフィシャルサイトで売っているお店を検索することもできるので
You can also search for stores selling them on the official Gashapon website,
ぜひ参考にしてください！
so please check it out!
ということで一番くじもガシャポンもよろしくねー！
So, please check out both Ichiban Kuji and Gashapon!
よろしくねー！
Please check them out!
ガシャポンしに行こうぜ〜！
Let's go play Gashapon~!
スタート！
Start!
このあとは ReGLOSS 2周年記念配信！
Up next is the ReGLOSS 2nd Anniversary stream!
いったい何が起こるんだ！？ たのしみ〜
What on earth is going to happen!? I'm so excited~
ねー！でも配信の前に！
Yeah! But before the stream!
ReGLOSSの2周年に関する沢山のお知らせをみんなで振り返っちゃいまーす！
Let's review lots of announcements about ReGLOSS's 2nd Anniversary together!
イエーイ！
Yay!
じゃあまずは記念グッズ！
First up, anniversary merchandise!
ReGLOSS 2周年を記念したグッズが hololive production OFFICIAL SHOP と全国のHMVとHMV&BOOKSの店舗で販売中です！
Merchandise commemorating ReGLOSS's 2nd Anniversary is now available at the hololive production OFFICIAL SHOP and HMV and HMV&BOOKS stores nationwide!
ラインナップはこちら！
Here is the lineup!
おー！可愛いー！
Ooh! So cute!
いっぱいある！このね、トミノとかめっちゃ可愛い！
There's so much! The acrylic keychains are super cute!
R ReGLOSSね！トートバッグいいねー！
"R" for ReGLOSS! The tote bag is nice!
ねー、おしゃれー！チェキ全部揃えたいねー！
Yeah, stylish! I want to collect all the photo cards!
分かるー！チェキー！
I know, right! The photo cards!
ランダム缶バッジは HMV 限定商品になっているので、ぜひ全国の HMV と HMV&BOOKS にお越しください！
The random trading badges are HMV exclusive items, so please visit HMV and HMV&BOOKS nationwide!
お願いしまーす！
Please check them out!
そんな HMV と HMV&BOOKS で本日から開催中の
And held from today at HMV and HMV&BOOKS...
「ReGLOSS 2nd Anniversary フェア」についても、おさらいです！
...here is a recap of the "ReGLOSS 2nd Anniversary Fair"!
今回のフェアではホロライブグッズを税込2,200円お買い上げごとに
At this fair, for every 2,200 yen (incl. tax) spent on hololive goods...
限定クリアカードをランダムで1枚プレゼントしちゃいます！
...you will receive 1 random exclusive clear card as a bonus!
やったー！
Yay!
フェアは10月5日まで！みんな楽しんでねー！
The fair runs until October 5th! Everyone, enjoy!
そして！
And!
2周年記念のボイスも販売中です！
Anniversary voice packs are also on sale!
今回は「旅」をコンセプトにしたボイスで、シチュエーションボイスと掛け合いボイスドラマの2種類があります！
This time, the voice packs are based on the concept of "traveling," featuring situation voices and dialogue drama voices!
な、なんと！旅行の準備をしてる様子であったりとか
What! It includes scenes of preparing for a trip...
あとは移動中の様子...
...and scenes while traveling...
なんかをね、ReGLOSSと一緒に旅のワクワクを味わえること間違いなしのボイスとなっております！
...letting you experience the excitement of traveling together with ReGLOSS!
ぜひ何度でも聴いて楽しんでください！
Please listen as many times as you like and enjoy!
楽しんでねー！
Enjoy!
いやーまさか螺鈿ちゃんがな、旅行前にあんなことするなんて
I can't believe Raden did that before the trip...
確かになー
Seriously...
柄にもないことしちゃったなー！だよねー！
Doing something so out of character! Right?!
はい、ということで ReGLOSS の2周年は超・超・超盛り沢山！
So, ReGLOSS's 2nd Anniversary is super, super packed with content!
GLOSSER もそうでない人もみんなで盛り上がっちゃいましょー！
Whether you're a GLOSSER or not, let's all get hyped together!
イエーイ！
Yay!
このあとの2周年記念配信でも何やら特大の発表があるとか！？
Word has it there's a huge announcement during the 2nd Anniversary stream right after this!?
心当たりが無さすぎる...
I have absolutely no idea...
心当たりあって！？すんごい特大のあれだよあれ！
How can you not know!? It's that huge thing!
皆さん最後まで絶対に見逃さないようにしてね！
Everyone, make sure you don't miss it until the very end!
はーい！
Okay!
それでは配信スタートまでもうしばらくお待ちくださーい！
Please wait a little longer until the stream starts!
せーの！ ReGLOSS でした〜！
One, two... That was ReGLOSS~!
巨大なソーセージが...
A giant sausage...
え、何？
Wait, what?
みんな気をつけて！
Everyone, watch out!
なんかめっちゃいびきうるさい奴がいる！
There's someone snoring super loudly!
やばいよ！
This is bad!
らでちゃんじゃない？
Isn't it Raden-chan?
ん...
Nn...
そんな... 宝飾じゃない、海なんて...
No way... It's not jewels, a sea like that...
泳げないよ...
I can't swim...
待って、気をつけてね！
Wait, be careful!
なんか...
Like...
今目の前に「後ろを振り向いてはいけない、席を立ってはいけない」って書いてある！
Right now in front of me, it says "Do not look behind, do not stand up"!
書いてあるわ！
It's written there!
もしかしたら振り向いたら... 死ぬのかも！
Maybe if we turn around... we'll die!
試してみようぜ！
Let's try it out!
じゃあ奏試してみて！
Then Kanade, try it out!
これまだ夢か？夢っぽいな、これまだ。
Is this still a dream? It feels like a dream.
ちょ、夢じゃないよ、奏ちゃん。
Wait, it's not a dream, Kanade-chan.
夢じゃないよ。
It's not a dream.
ていうか、あ！なんか出てきたよ！
Wait, ah! Something popped up!
お、何？
Oh, what is it?
えっと、読み上げるね。
Um, I'll read it out.
「聞こえますか... ReGLOSSのみなさん...」
"Can you hear me... members of ReGLOSS..."
「私はこの部屋に封印されたお宝...」
"I am a treasure sealed in this room..."
「今...あなたたちの心に直接呼びかけています...」
"Now... I am speaking directly to your hearts..."
なんだって！？
What did you say?!
「今から、あなたたちに2年目最後の試練を与えます...」
"Now, I shall give you the final trial of your second year..."
「みなさんで謎を解いて、3年目への扉を開けてください」
"Solve the mystery together and open the door to your third year."
「謎解きのルールは簡単です...」
"The rules of the puzzle are simple..."
「4文字のキーワードを見つけ出すのです...」
"Find the 4-character keyword..."
おー！
Oh!
「ただし、席を立ってはいけません...」
"However, you must not stand up from your seat..."
「真後ろだけは振り向いてもいけません...ルールはそれだけです...」
"You must not look directly behind you... Those are the only rules..."
ふむふむ。
Mm-hmm.
「キーワードがわかったら、一人ずつ順番に読み上げてくだい...」
"Once you figure out the keyword, read it out one by one in order..."
「みなさんの絆なら、必ずクリアできるでしょう...」
"With your bond, you will surely be able to clear it..."
「それでは、開始です」
"Now, let us begin."
「さあ、みなさんで 3年目の扉を開けるのです」
"Now, open the door to the third year together."
もう3年目始まってる...
The third year has already started...
扉を開けるも何も、まだ開けられてなかったってこと？
Open the door or not, does that mean we couldn't open it yet?
なるほどね。
I see.
じゃあとりあえず、なんか目の前にさ...
So anyway, in front of us...
なんかあるね！これ何だ？
There's something! What is this?
なんかパズルっぽいのか？
Is it like a puzzle?
ね、クロスワードっぽいやつが置いてない？
Hey, isn't there a crossword-like thing placed here?
あ、本当だ！
Ah, it's true!
なんだろう？あんこ？
What is it? Anko?
あんこ？
Anko?
なんかバラバラになったひらがな読んだだけだから関係ないやつね。
I just read the scattered hiragana, so it's unrelated.
奏のは「だー」！
Kanade's is "Daa"!
はじめのは「いんぐ」！
Hajime's is "Ingu"!
いんぐ？
Ingu?
それさ、問題じゃなくてさ...
That's not the clue...
クロスワードの埋まってる部分だけ言ってるよね？
You're just reading the filled-in parts of the crossword, right?
え？本当？
Eh? Really?
じゃあ、一旦リリカのヨコの鍵の1番言うね！
Okay, first I'll read my number 1 horizontal clue!
ある飲み物を作るとき...
When making a certain beverage...
精米歩合を 50% 以上 60% 以下で作るとこう呼ばれる。
When made with a rice-polishing ratio between 50% and 60%, it is called this.
あ！これ「吟醸」じゃない？！
Ah! Isn't this "Ginjo"?!
なにそれ？
What's that?
ごめん、1ミリも聞いてなかった、ごめん。
Sorry, I wasn't listening at all, sorry.
なんだよ！
What the heck!
ある飲み物を作るとき...
When making a certain beverage...
精米歩合を 50% 以上 60% 以下で作るとこう呼ばれる。
When made with a rice-polishing ratio between 50% and 60%, it is called this.
じゅまい？じゅまいしゅ？
Jumai? Jumaishu?
「ぎ」から始まる言葉で「う」で終わるのだから「吟醸」じゃないかなって思ったんだけど...
It starts with "gi" and ends with "u", so I thought it might be "Ginjo"...
えー、博識！そうなんだ！
Whoa, so knowledgeable! I see!
え、違うかな？
Wait, is it wrong?
えー、わかんない！
Eh, I don't know!
でも「ぎ」から始まって「う」で終わる言葉、他に知らないから、それでいいんじゃない？
But I don't know any other word starting with "gi" and ending with "u", so isn't that fine?
いいじゃん、いいじゃん！書いちゃえ！
Nice, nice! Write it down!
じゃあ次、らでんちゃん、なんかある？
Then next, Raden-chan, do you have something?
えっと...ねぇ...
Um... well...
えっと...ちょっと待って、今問題がガチすぎて...
Um... wait a moment, the questions are so serious...
ちょっと今、頭が真っ白になって...一旦別の人に！
My mind went completely blank right now... pass to someone else for a moment!
じゃあ奏、どうかな？
Then Kanade, how about you?
えっと、丸1の横が...
Um, horizontal number 1 is...
コツはタンギング。身近だけど奥深い。
The key is tonguing. Familiar yet deep.
あー！
Ah!
タンギング？
Tonguing?
タタタタとかなんじゃないの？
Isn't it like ta-ta-ta-ta?
やばい、全然分かんない！
Oh no, I have no idea!
タ・タ・タンギング...タチツテトなのかな？
Ta-ta-tonguing... Is it ta-chi-tsu-te-to?
かな？
Maybe?
分かった！良い事考えた！一旦みんな自分の問題を読んで、分かるやつを埋めよう！
Got it! I have a good idea! Let's all read our own questions first and fill in the ones we know!
で、分からないやつを相談する形にしよう！
And then let's consult each other on the ones we don't know!
そうだね、喋ってたらあまり時間がなくなる気がしちゃうから。
Right, because if we keep talking, I feel like we'll run out of time.
時間とかあるのかよく分からないけど。
I don't really know if there's a time limit, though.
あは！これ分かるよ！
Aha! I know this one!
お！
Oh!
丸4... 4文字分かればいいってこと？
Number 4... So I just need to figure out 4 characters?
エモく味付け...
Emotionally seasoning...
料理の味加減？
The seasoning of cooking?
なんか優しいな...
It's kind of gentle...
え、奏分かったよ！
Eh, Kanade figured it out!
お！全部分かった？
Oh! Did you figure out all of them?
いや、全部分かんないけど丸4が分かるから...
No, I don't know all of them, but I know number 4...
キーワードナンバー3が分かりました！
So I figured out Keyword Number 3!
お！
Oh!
キーワードのナンバー3はじゃあ何だったか 奏は
What was Kanade's keyword for number 3?
えっと
Um...
丸4が混ぜ混ぜして食べる料理 お好みにコチュジャンをかけてって書いてあったから ビビンバで
Number 4 said "A dish eaten mixed together, add gochujang to taste," so it was bibimbap...
あー 確かに
Ah, true!
その最後のワードの「ば」でした
So the last letter of that word was "ba".
ばーか
Idiot!
ば？ ばって何だ？ 何ば？
"Ba"? What's "ba"? What "ba"?
何も無いぞ
There's nothing there.
じゃあ「ば」ね
So "ba", right?
え、ごめん リリカね どっちもわかんなくて
Uh, sorry, Ao and Lirika, I don't understand either of them.
何？
What?
あの 4番目「物事の具合をうまく処理すること」
Number 4: "Handling the state of things well"...
「料理の味加減についても言う」っていうのが... ごめん 料理関係は本当にわからない
"...and also used to refer to food seasoning." Sorry, I really don't get cooking stuff!
えー！ 料理系VTuberじゃなかったのー！？
Ehh?! Weren't you a cooking VTuber?!
もう引退した方がいいかも 料理系
Maybe I should retire from cooking...
物事の具合をうまく処理することって何？
What is "handling the state of things well"?
ちょうりつ？
Chouritsu (Harmonization)?
ほう でも味加減のことそう言うかな？
Oh... But would you call seasoning that?
味加減？
Seasoning?
調整？
Chousei (Adjustment)?
ベロ？
Bero (Tongue)?
なんか練習し始めちゃった
She started practicing something!
あじ... あじ...
Seasoning... Seasoning...
これさ 振り向いちゃいけないんだよね？
Hey, we're not allowed to turn around, right?
ダメだよ
You can't.
このさ イラスト何なの？
What is this illustration anyway?
え どこまでじゃあ振り向いちゃいけない... どこまで見ていいものなの？
Wait, how far are we not allowed to turn around... how far can we look?
真後ろを見たらダメって言ってた
They said looking directly behind is not allowed.
あ、横はいいんだ
Ah, sideways is okay then.
横はいいんだ
Sideways is fine.
横 えーっと リリカ？ はい
Sideways, um, Lirika? Yes.
奏側の横に何かない？
Is there something next to Kanade's side?
奏側の横に... なんか人を殺せそうなバットが置いてある
Next to Kanade's side... There's a bat that looks like it could kill someone.
バットー！？
A bat?!
あとリコーダーもある
And a recorder too.
バットとリコーダー？ うん
A bat and a recorder? Yeah.
バットでいいんだね それは
A bat is fine then, for that?
トゲトゲしたバット 鬼の金棒みたいな感じ
A spiked bat. Like an oni's spiked club.
鬼の金棒？
An oni's spiked club?
うん なるほど ありがとう
Yeah. I see, thank you.
自分の位置から見えてんじゃん あーー！ 番長の場所！
You can see it from your own position! Ahhh! Bancho's place!
え？ 何もわからないジャン
Eh? You can't tell anything from here.
なんか分からないのあった？
Was there one you didn't get?
これ アーモンドのような香りがする危険な薬品
This one: "A dangerous chemical that smells like almonds"...
シアン化カリウムのまたの名前って何や？
What's another name for potassium cyanide?
え、むずい！
Eh, that's hard!
滑舌が何て言ったか今分からなかった
I couldn't understand what you said with that pronunciation!
アーモンドみたいな香りがする危険な薬品 シアン化カリウム またの名前は何や？
A dangerous chemical with an almond smell, potassium cyanide, what's another name for it?
青酸カリとかじゃないの？
Isn't it seisankari (potassium cyanide)?
天才やん！
You're a genius!
せーちゃんカリか
Sei-chan-kari?
文字数合ってる？ 合ってるわ！
Does the character count match? It matches!
すごーい！ ありがちゅん
Awesome! Thank you~
オッケー いいじゃん
Okay. Nice!
え？ あとは...
Eh? What's left...
わかった
Got it.
リリカのね ヒントが 反対側の椅子の背中に書かれている文字が入るってなってて
Lirika's hint says "Contains the letter written on the back of the chair opposite you."
多分リリカの反対が番長なんだよね うん
The one opposite Lirika is probably Bancho. Yeah.
だかららでんちゃんか奏かどっちか番長の背中見れない？ あ、らでん見ます
So can Raden or Kanade look at Bancho's back? Ah, I'll look.
「ん」って書いてあるよ ん？ ん？ ん！
It says "n"! "N"? "N"? "N"!
「ん」か ってことは料理の味加減のやつが 2文字目が「ん」なんだけどそれで4文字
"N", huh? That means the cooking seasoning one has "n" as the 2nd letter, making it 4 letters total.
味加減？
Seasoning?
料理の味加減についても言うし 物事の具合をうまく処理すること
Used for food seasoning, and also for handling the state of things well.
盤面処理とか... もうダメだ カードゲームの頭しか出てこない
Board control... I'm hopeless, I can only think in card game terms!
4文字か
4 letters, huh?
〇ん〇〇だよね
? n ? ?, right?
感覚... あ！ 分かったかもしれない！ あんばい！
Kankaku (Sensation)... Ah! I might have got it! Anbai (Seasoning / Balance)!
あー！ それかも！ えーすごい！
Ah! That might be it! Eh, amazing!
あんばい？ それかも！ 分かんない！
Anbai? Might be! I don't know!
だーとリリカの最初のキーワード「あ」かも
Then Lirika's first keyword might be "a".
あ... あ、ん、ば、い え？
A... A-n-ba-i. Eh?
このキーワードね あ、そうね 並べた時に
The keywords, right. Ah, yeah, when lined up.
番長はあと何が分かってない？ えっと 4番だけ分かってないんだけど
What does Bancho still not know? Um, only number 4 isn't solved yet...
あの ヒントは反対側の椅子の背中だから リリカ？の背中？
Um, the hint is "back of the chair opposite", so is it Lirika's chair back?
問題は？ えっと ストリートダンス クランプでの特徴的な振り付け ストンプ チェストポップ あと1つは？
What's the question? "A signature move in krump street dance. Stomp, chest pop, and one more is...?"
何だろう？ リリカの背中を見てあげて
What could it be? Look at Lirika's back for her.
「す」 おい誰も見ねえのかよ！
"Su"! Hey, is nobody looking?!
誰も見れないよ！ 待って リリカの背中見たらいいんだね？ そう！
Nobody can see! Wait, I just need to look at Lirika's back, right? Yes!
はい 「す」 「す」が入る ダンスのやつ
Okay. "Su". It starts with "su". The dance move.
スリップ？ 違う それは脱ぐこと？
Slip? No. Is that taking off clothes?
ステップ... す... スクー...
Step... Su... Sku...
す... すみません！ すみません 全然分かんない
Su... Sumimasen (Sorry)! Sumimasen. I have no idea.
すみません ちょっとぶった切ってしまって申し訳ないんですが らでんちゃんのほう行こう
Sorry, I'm terribly sorry to interrupt, but... Let's go to Raden-chan's.
誰か私の背中に書かれている文字を読んで欲しいです 「び」です
Someone please read the character written on my back. It's "bi".
び？ ばびぶべぼの「び」？ そう
"Bi"? The "bi" in ba-bi-bu-be-bo? Yes.
どんな問題？ えっとね 江戸時代に...
What's the question? Well, in the Edo period...
...に、こそでの色として流行した青色の名前... 宝石ラピスラズリの和名や、ガラスの昔の呼び方が含まれて...
"...became popular as the color for kosode; the Japanese name for lapis lazuli and an ancient term for glass are contained within..."
ガチすぎだろこれ！
"This is way too hardcore!"
問題が難しすぎて、一瞬で頭パーンってなっちゃったよ、最初！
"The questions were so hard, my brain just went blank for a second at first!"
「す」が入ってるんだ。
"There's a 'Su' in it."
ココッシュなのかな？
"Could it be 'Kokosh'?"
美白とか、微琥珀...
"Bihaku (whitening), or... micro-amber..."
最初の1文字が「こ」なんだよね。「こ・び・ふむふむ」
"The first character is 'Ko', right? 'Ko - Bi - hmm'."
へぇ〜
"I see."
こ、こび...こびり...こびり...こ...
"Ko... kobi... kobiri... kobiri... ko..."
やばい、私全然浮かばないんだけど！
"Oh no, nothing is coming to mind at all!"
えー、分かんにゃいぞ？
"Ehh, I don't get it at all."
こび...こび...コバルトブルー！
"Kobi... kobi... Cobalt Blue!"
違う...
"No..."
あ、でも多分これかな...
"Ah, but maybe it's this..."
何？ 番長、なんかあった？
"What? Bancho, did you get something?"
え、なんか... あー、「いんぐ」ってなるんだけど...
"Eh, well... Ah, it ends in 'ingu', but..."
うん。
"Yeah."
「しゅ」が入るって言ってたじゃん？ で、アームシューイングかな？ みたいな...
"You said there's a 'shu' in it, right? So I thought maybe 'Arm swinging'..."
あー！ おー！
"Ah! Oh!"
でも分からん、そんな言葉知らんかった...
"But I don't know, I've never heard of such a word..."
なるほどね...
"I see..."
生み出しちゃった、言葉を。
"I just created a word."
生み出しちゃったか〜 生み出しちゃったか〜
"You created one, huh? You created one~"
いや、いいじゃん。
"Well, that's fine."
他に番長から連線で、なんかヒントになりそうなものない？
"Is there anything else near Bancho that could be a hint?"
この問題解ければ行けるかもな、みたいな...
"Like, 'If we solve this question, we might be able to move forward'..."
えーっとね、4番が「こ・び・」
"Let's see, number 4 is 'Ko - Bi -'"
「せ」
"'Se'"
リリナーデの間にあったのは、トゲトゲのバットだったんだよね？
"What was between Ririnade was a spiked bat, right?"
トゲトゲのバットとリコーダー。
"A spiked bat and a recorder."
そう、トゲトゲのバットってさ、なんかトゲトゲのバット以外の言い方ってない？
"Yeah, is there any other way to say 'spiked bat'?"
金棒！
"Kanabo!"
金棒？
"Kanabo?"
あ、だから2文字目に「ん」が来る！
"Ah, so there's an 'N' as the second character!"
「ん」？
"'N'?"
「ん」が来る。
"An 'N' comes next."
「棍棒」じゃない？
"Isn't it 'Konbo' (club)?"
あー！
"Ah!"
それじゃない？！
"Isn't that it?!"
棍棒...
"Konbo..."
棍棒って言うよね！
"You call it a konbo, right!"
待って！ 最初自分の問題書いて間違ってる説ある？
"Wait! Is there a chance I wrote down my own question wrong at the start?"
え、ちょっと待って！ それ...
"Eh, wait a sec! That..."
どこだっけ？
"Where was it?"
え、この色で写真を加工するとエモくなり勝ち...
"Eh, 'Processing a photo with this color tends to make it look emotional'..."
セピア！
"Sepia!"
え、合ってるよね？
"Eh, that's right, isn't it?"
いや、分かんない、もう！
"Ugh, I don't know anymore!"
え、何何？ 全部読んでみて！
"Eh, what what? Read the whole thing!"
え、元々はイカ墨のことだったって。
"Eh, 'It originally referred to cuttlefish ink.'"
モノトーンとか？ モノクロ？
"Monotone? Monochrome?"
いや、でも3文字なんだよね。
"No, but it's 3 characters."
で、セピアだと思って...しかも青酸カリにも繋がるし...
"And I thought it was Sepia... plus it connects to Potassium Cyanide..."
うん、うん、うん。
"Yeah, yeah, yeah."
で、パーティー会場で使うハンマーは、ピコピコハンマー？
"And the hammer used at party venues is a Pikopiko Hammer?"
うん、うん、うん、うん。
"Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah."
で、埋まってるんだよ。
"So that's filled in."
じゃあ、そのダンスのやつだけ分かんないんだ。
"Then only that dance one is left unsolved."
そう。
"Right."
で、「あ」から始まって「しゅ」が付くんだったら、「スイング」にはなるだろうなっていうので...
"And if it starts with 'A' and has 'Shu', it'll probably be 'swing'..."
「あ・1文字・や」
"'A - [1 char] - Ya'"
あっち1文字だったら「腕」かな？ みたいな...
"If that part is one character, maybe 'Ude' (arm)?"
ほうほうほう。
"I see, I see."
思ったんだけど...
"That's what I thought..."
「アーム」ってこと？
"You mean 'Arm'?"
そう。
"Yeah."
で、それで番長のワードは何になるの？
"So what does Bancho's word become?"
キーワードは「む」になる。
"The keyword becomes 'Mu'."
なるほど。
"I see."
「あ・ば・む」ってこと？
"So it's 'A - Ba - Mu'?"
いや、「アルバム」じゃねぇかよ！
"Wait, isn't that 'Album'?!"
「アルバム」じゃねぇか！ 他にあるの？！ 逆から考えよう、ラデンちゃん！
"That's totally 'Album'! Is there anything else?! Let's think backwards, Raden-chan!"
はーい！
"Yeees!"
「あ・ば・む」の中で「ん」の中に入る言葉、なんかあるかな？
"Inside 'A - Ba - Mu'... is there any character that can fit in the middle?"
うーん...
"Hmm..."
味バムとか？
"'Aji-bamu' (flavoring)...?"
味バム？
"Aji-bamu?"
足バム？
"Ashi-bamu?"
汗ばむ！
"Asebamu (sweating)!"
あ、汗ばむいい感じ！
"Ah, 'Asebamu' sounds good!"
いいね！
"Nice!"
キーワードナンバー2なんですけど...
"For keyword number 2..."
「る」のような気がしています。
"I feel like it's 'Ru'."
いや、今もうその話出てるでしょ！
"Hey, we're already talking about that!"
なんでだよ！
"Why, of all times?!"
いや、なんか難しく考えすぎてたんだな。
"Ah, well... I guess we were overthinking it."
もういいかもしれない。
"Maybe we're good now."
あ、じゃあ特にラピスラズリの和名が分かったとかじゃなくて、なんとなく「る」な気が...
"Ah, so it wasn't that you figured out lapis lazuli's Japanese name, but just a hunch that it was 'Ru'..."
あんね、多分「こびるり」のような気がするんだけど...
"You see, I feel like it's 'Kobiruri', but..."
ラデン側にすごい問題が起きていて、何が問題かっていうと...
"There's a huge problem on Raden's side. What's the problem? Well..."
ラデンの周りに色々ヒントがあるのは、なんとなく分かってはいるんだけど...
"I kinda realize there are various hints around Raden, but..."
目が悪すぎてさ、何を表しているのか全く見えない！
"My eyesight is so terrible that I can't see what they represent at all!"
ラデンちゃんの隣にはピストルがあるよ。
"There's a pistol next to Raden-chan."
ピストルね。
"A pistol, okay."
うん。あと、なんかもう1個ない？
"Yeah. And isn't there another one?"
なんか...
"Like..."
目悪くて全然見えないよ！
"My eyes are bad, so I can't see at all!"
絵画っぽいんだけど...
"It looks like a painting, but..."
なんかお馬さんなのか、羊なのか、何かに乗ってる...
"Riding on something... like a horse, or a sheep..."
なんか牛じゃない、これ？
"Isn't this a cow?"
これ牛なの？！
"Is that a cow?!"
広い草原みたいなところで...
"In a broad grassy field..."
黒い物体と白い物体がフュージョンしてる...
"A black object and a white object are fusing together..."
いやいや、人がお馬さんに乗ってるんじゃない、これ？
"No no, isn't a person riding a horse here?"
ありがとう！
"Thank you!"
キーワードナンバー2は何になってるの？
"What is keyword number 2 now?"
「る」です。
"It's 'Ru'."
まったく想像がつかない！ 体が後ろ向きだから見れないんだけど！
"I can't imagine at all! My body is facing backward, so I can't see it!"
もういいよ、ラデグロス！ 俺ら「アルバム」で行こうぜ！
"Whatever, Radegloss! Let's just go with 'Album'!"
分かんないけど！ なんかっぽいよね！ っぽいよね！
"I don't know, but it sounds like it! Sounds like it!"
それで行こう！
"Let's go with that!"
じゃあ、キーワード1、「ア」！
"Alright, Keyword 1: 'A'!"
キーワード2、「ル」！
"Keyword 2: 'Ru'!"
キーワードナンバー3、「バ」！
"Keyword Number 3: 'Ba'!"
キーワードナンバー4、「ム」！
"Keyword Number 4: 'Mu'!"
せーの！
Ready, set...
アルバム！
Album!
す... どや？ どや？
Su... How's that? How's that?
もう振り向いちゃいけないの... 何これ？ まだじゃない？
We shouldn't turn back around... Wait, what's this? Isn't it too early?
振り向くよ！ 振り向くよ！
Turn around! Turn around!
振り向いちゃえ！ なんかある！ えっ！ すごーい！
Let me turn around! There's something! Eh! Wow!
じゃあちょっと宝箱に向かってさっきの呪文もう一回唱えるか！
Alright, let's face the treasure chest and chant that spell one more time!
呪文何だっけ？ アルバムね！
What was the spell? "Album"!
行くよ！ せーの！ アルバム！
Here we go! Ready, set... Album!
どうだ？ わー！ 脱出成功！
How is it? Wow! Escape successful!
脱出成功！ こんな難しい問題生でやらせんな！
Escape successful! Don't make us solve such hard puzzles live!
危ねぇ！
That was dangerous!
コケないでよかったわー！ 怖かったー！ 本当にこれ...
Glad nobody tripped! That was scary! Seriously, this...
なんか「HAPPY ANNIVERSARY」って書いてある！ ハッピーアニバーサリー！
It says "HAPPY ANNIVERSARY"! Happy Anniversary!
ハッピーアニバーサリーじゃない！ ハッピーになれて良かったね！
It's not Happy Anniversary! But I'm glad we got to be happy!
この配信前にスタッフさんが「いや簡単、すごい簡単だから」って言ってて...
Before this stream, the staff said "No, it's easy, really easy"...
美術検定受けてんのかと思ってびっくりした！
I thought I was taking an art test, I was so shocked!
それぞれがちょっと得意っぽい分野の問題になってたのは良かったね
It was nice that each puzzle was tuned to things we're good at.
知らねぇよ！ 全然やることなかった！
I don't know about that! I had nothing to do!
ビビンバで終わっちゃった！
It ended with bibimbap!
はい！ ということで、皆様もうお分かりかと思いますけれども、まずはこちらの映像をご覧ください！
Alright! So as you all might have guessed by now, please check out this video first!
さっきの文字が難しかった話でみんなで笑いながら... すみません、VTRの裏でちょっと話してました...
We were all laughing about how hard those letters were... Sorry, we were chatting while the video played!
はい！ ということでですね、なんとReGLOSSの2ndアルバムが11月12日に発売決定！
Yes! So, ReGLOSS's 2nd album is confirmed for release on November 12th!
イエーイ！
Yay!
アルバムのタイトルは『Snapshot』！ パシャ、パシャ。スナップ写真のように日々の暮らしに寄り添い、時に共に時を重ねていけるような、そんなアルバムになっています！
The album title is "Snapshot"! Snap, snap. Just like snapshot photos, it's an album that fits into daily life so we can share moments together!
はい！ 今回のアルバムは、ホロライブ公式ECサイト限定の「完全生産限定盤」と「通常盤」の2種類あります！
Yes! This album comes in two editions: the Hololive Official EC Site Limited "Complete Limited Edition" and the "Standard Edition"!
完全生産限定盤は、海外のおもちゃを彷彿とさせるブリスターパック仕様で、
The Complete Limited Edition features blister pack packaging reminiscent of overseas toys,
CDのほかに、アルバムの衣装と同じデニム風の雰囲気が可愛い、カメラ型トレカケース！
and along with the CD, it includes a cute camera-style photocard case with a denim look matching the album outfits!
リリースされたばかりのソロ曲のビジュアルを使用したソロシリーズカードセット！
A solo series card set featuring visuals from the newly released solo tracks!
そして、複製コメント入りランダムプロフィールカード1枚がランダムでついてきますよ！
And 1 random profile card with printed comments is included at random!
通常盤は全国流通もしまして、初回プレス分限定の封入特典として、ランダムミニカードが1枚封入されています！
The Standard Edition will be distributed nationwide, and as a first-press limited bonus, 1 random mini card is included!
詳細はSNSや今後順次発表される各販売店の情報をチェックしてください！
For details, please check social media and retailer info to be announced sequentially!
ホロライブ公式ECサイトの予約は、この時間からスタート！
Pre-orders on the Hololive Official EC site start right now!
予約ページのリンクが表示されていると思いますので、チェックしてください！
Links to the pre-order page should be displayed, so please check them out!
さらに！ 店舗別特典のラインナップも公開しちゃいます！
Furthermore, we are revealing the lineup for store-exclusive bonuses!
絵柄など詳しい情報はまた後日公開予定です！
Detailed info like designs will be revealed at a later date!
また、このアルバムに収録されている楽曲はデジタルでの配信も予定しておりますので、お楽しみに！
Also, the tracks included on this album are scheduled for digital release, so look forward to it!
よろしくお願いします！ そして、2ndアルバムのリリースを記念して、今年もリリースイベントの開催が決定しました！
Thank you! And to celebrate the 2nd album release, a release event is confirmed to take place again this year!
期間内に対象商品をHMV&BOOKS onlineにて全額前金でご予約いただいた方の中から、抽選でご当選された方をリリース記念イベントにご招待！
Those who pre-order eligible items with full advance payment on HMV&BOOKS online during the offer period will be entered into a draw to be invited to the release event!
今回は、第1部 リリなで、第2部 らではじめ となっております！
This time, Part 1 features Riri-Nade, and Part 2 features Rade-Hajime!
応募待ってるよー！
We're waiting for your applications!
待って、配信始まってる... ライブ会場向かってる途中じゃなかったっけ？
Wait... Weren't we supposed to be heading to the live venue?
そうだっけ？ ライブ会場行く途中... そっか！
Is that so? On our way to the live venue... Oh right!
ということで、このあとミニライブ！ 本日MVが公開された「Our Time Yellow」のパフォーマンスもあるんで、最後まで見てくださいね！
So coming up next is a mini live! We also have a performance of "Our Time Yellow", whose MV was released today, so watch until the end!
ライブ中にもまた重大発表があるとか、あるとか？！
Will there be another major announcement during the live performance too?!
まだまだ2周年記念配信は始まったばかり！ ほな、急いでライブ会場にいらっしゃーい！
The 2nd anniversary stream has only just begun! Now then, hurry over to the live venue!
着替えー！
Change clothes!
着替えてステップちょうだい！ 行こう！
Change and give me some steps! Let's go!
ここ本当ライブ会場に繋がんの？
Does this really connect to the concert venue?
眩しい！ ドアデカっ！
It's so bright! The doors are huge!
行け行け行け行けー！
Go, go, go, go!
着替えよっか。
Shall we change?
着替えよー！
Let's change!
あ、やば、チャック引っかかった！
Ah, crap, my zipper got stuck!
大丈夫？
Are you okay?
代わって代わって！ 痛い痛い痛い！
Let me help! Ouch, ouch, ouch!
直った！ 助かったー！
It's fixed! Thank goodness!
ジャージだからまた買ってもらおう。
It's just a tracksuit, so let's get another pair bought.
変な汗かきすぎて冷や汗が止まらなかったよ！
I broke out in such a weird sweat, the cold sweat wouldn't stop!
難しかった？
Was it hard?
いや、なんかね、予想外だった。
No, it was kind of unexpected.
なぞなぞみたいなのが出てくるのかと思ってたの。
I thought we'd get riddles or something.
普通に雑学というか知識ゲーだったね！
It was straight-up trivia and knowledge-based!
超びっくりした。 知識を始めに求めんな！
I was super surprised. Don't demand knowledge from the start!
解けないじゃん！
We can't solve that!
生産狩りちょっと答えられなかったの悔しいわ。
I'm annoyed I couldn't answer the primary producer hunting question.
あんま日常で「これは生産狩り」って見たことあるの？
Have you ever seen anyone point out "primary producer hunting" in real life?
そうね。知ってるやつあんまないもんな。
True. We didn't really know most of those.
そろそろか？
Is it about time?
何歌う？
What are we singing?
今から決める感じ！？
We're deciding right now?!
カラオケじゃないんだから！
This isn't karaoke!
カラオケのノリなんだけど。何歌う？ 何にしようかねー。
It feels like karaoke vibes. What should we sing?
踊りながら歌えるやつがいいんじゃない？
Wouldn't something we can sing while dancing be good?
踊りながら！？ ハードル高いことするねー！
While dancing?! Setting the bar high, aren't we?!
LAKI MODE
止められない雲の上
Above the unstoppable clouds
星舞って
Stars dancing
流れて落ちてきた光にまたがって
Riding on the light that came streaming down
一瞬の冬日交わそう
Let's exchange a fleeting winter sun
名無しの星たちが 嬉々としてステップ刻んだ
Unnamed stars joyfully carved out their steps
我が物顔でなびく アイソレーション クールに決めて魅せる
Swaying with an air of ownership, pulling off cool isolations
冴えない夢には大爆笑 鼻先が似合いそう
Bursting into laughter at dull dreams, fitting right on the tip of the nose
色んな服着てパレード 踊ろう
Dressing up in various outfits, let me dance in the parade
you under the starlight
流れに身を委ねて ただただ漂うだけのハート
Surrendering to the flow, a heart that merely floats along
君だけのプレイリスト マイクフロウ 耳元まで運ぶよ
Your very own playlist, mic flow, delivered right to your ears
ドンピシャなモーション ドンピシャなキモ
Spot-on motion, spot-on mood
闇を照らすオーロラ 言葉選ぶのオンリーワン
An aurora illuminating the dark, choosing words as an only one
踊ってたい ずっと
I want to keep dancing forever
またとないこの日を 降り注ぐプラズマ 君がいれば plus one
This irreplaceable day, pouring plasma, with you it's plus one
色濃く映そう ビビッドなハイライト
Let me project them vividly, vivid highlights
病みつきになるダンスダンス 灰になるまで ice ice
Addictive dance, dance, ice ice until we turn to ash
寝ても覚めても 華やぐトワイライト
Awake or asleep, a glamorous twilight
きらめいたら nice nice もっと光り ice ice
When it sparkles, it's nice nice, shining brighter, ice ice
ありがとう！
Thank you!
次は SUPER DUPER! バチバチノリノリでフィートオーバー... 始まり！
Next is SUPER DUPER! Super hyped up, feet over... Here we start!
散らついた胸の奥 愛してやまないもの 疑うことも知らぬまま
Flickering deep inside my heart, things I love endlessly, without ever doubting
そう射止める覚悟はできているよ
Yes, I'm ready to capture it all
Gimme that Gimme that 未来だ
Gimme that, gimme that future
SUPER DUPER 音触るのシャングリラ 日が暮れるまで踊ろうよ
SUPER DUPER, touching sound in Shangri-La, let's dance until the sun sets
誰が何と言おうと 気にしないリミッター 解放
No matter what anyone says, release the limiters without care
ただ楽しむだけ 眩しい声を響かせて
Just enjoy it all, let your dazzling voice resound
Yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah ah ah
俯いた世界を変えてみせよう
Let's show them we can change this downcast world
Yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah SUPER DUPER
一喜一憂も 一滴の息注いで 一心同体でいて
Even with every tear and joy, pouring a single breath, remaining as one
容赦なく恋したメロディと 会えなくて手放したフリが
The melody I fell helplessly in love with, pretending to let go when we couldn't meet
名もなき君との境界線を超えリプレイ
Crossing the boundary line with you, unnamed, replay!
SUPER DUPER 音触るのシャングリラ 日が暮れるまで踊ろうよ
SUPER DUPER, touching sound in Shangri-La, let's dance until the sun sets
誰が何と言おうと 気にしないリミッター 解放
No matter what anyone says, release the limiters without care
ただ楽しむだけ 眩しい声を響かせて
Just enjoy it all, let your dazzling voice resound
Yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah ah ah
俯いた世界を変えてみせよう
Let's show them we can change this downcast world
Yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah SUPER DUPER
ありがとう！
Thank you!
次の曲は... bvdiz!
The next song is... bvdiz!
この曲ってことは... 盛り上がっていく準備はできてるよねー！？
Which means... you're all ready to get hyped up, right~!?
いくよー！
Here we go~!
オーキードーキー 既成概念壊さいか アノマリーズ
Okie dokie, breaking through stereotypes, anomalies
Easy breezy 歌いだせば Favourite
Easy breezy, once you start singing, it's a favourite
オーキードーキー このままリタイアなんて Easy breezy 踊ろうよ Everybody
Okie dokie, retiring just like this? Easy breezy, let me dance, everybody
それぞれ異なった価値観 混ざるほどノリノリマッチ
Different values blending together make a hyped-up match
ルールもなければ決まりもないゼロから始まる
No rules, no set bounds, starting from zero
愉快な仲間 壊せば倍増するサバイバル 妄想話し広げばっか騒ぎ
Fun friends, breaking limits doubles our survival, spreading wild talk and making noise
運命共同体 伝線してゆく喜怒哀楽
A shared fate, contagious joy, anger, grief, and pleasure
分かち合えるエンパシー 共に目指すは Reach the top!
Shared empathy, aiming together to Reach the top!
Reach the top! Yeah!
絶対絶対絶対絶対的キラチューン
Absolute, absolute, absolute killer tune
今は自由気まま水色つなぐユニバース
Right now, carefree, light blue connecting universe
ノリノリ ノリノリ シンクロするシナプス
Grooving, grooving, synchronizing synapses
限界突破 引きつけるミラクル
Breaking through limits, drawing in miracles
あれ？こんなところにカメラが！
Huh? There's a camera right here!
オーキードーキー 既成概念壊さいか アノマリーズ
Okie dokie, breaking through stereotypes, anomalies
easy breezy
歌い出せば favorite
When we start singing, it's our favorite
okey dokey このままでいたいよね
okey dokey, I want to stay like this
easy breezy 踊ろうよ everybody
easy breezy, let's dance everybody
一人ずつのレパ また一人も一緒に 会いたくなる気持ち
Each of our repertoires makes us want to meet again together
睦みのままならぬ もつながるプロローグ
Even if we aren't completely harmonious, it's a connected prologue
もう白紙だった僕らのストーリー みんなといる空間がExtreme
Our story that was once a blank page—being with everyone is extreme
描写するかけがえないメモリーズ さあ無理掴み行くNext dream
Depicting irreplaceable memories, now let's grasp the next dream
運命 共同体
A shared destiny
伝染していく喜怒哀楽
Emotions spreading and catching on
分かち合える
We can share
エンパシー 共に目指すは reach the top yeah
empathy, together aiming to reach the top yeah
絶対 絶対 絶対 絶対的キラーチューン
Absolute, absolute, absolute, absolute killer tune
今は自由気まま 水入らずなユニバース
Right now, carefree, a private universe just for us
reload re reload reload シナプス
reload re reload reload synapses
限界突破 惹きつけるミラクル
Breaking boundaries, a captivating miracle
okey dokey 史上最高な bv diz
okey dokey, the greatest bv diz in history
easy breezy 歌い出せば favorite
easy breezy, when we start singing, it's our favorite
okey dokey このままでいたいよね
okey dokey, I want to stay like this
easy breezy 踊ろうよ everybody
easy breezy, let me see everybody dance
ということで
So with that...
いつもの挨拶大丈夫？息途切れてない？大丈夫？
Is everyone ready for our usual greeting? Not out of breath? Are we good?
いつもの挨拶から行きますよ！
Let's start with our usual greeting!
リグロスオープン！ We are ReGLOSS!
ReGLOSS open! We are ReGLOSS!
はい！ということで、『ラクガキMODE』と『SUPER DUPER』、そして『bv diz』、3曲を聴いていただきました！
Alright! So with that, you listened to three songs: 'LAKUGAKI MODE', 'SUPER DUPER', and 'bv diz'!
皆さん盛り上がってますか～？
Is everyone hyped up~?
イエーイ！
Yay!
まだまだ足りない！盛り上がってますか～？
Still not enough! Are you hyped up~?
イエーイ！
Yay!
盛り上がってますか～？
Are you hyped up~?
イエーイ！
Yay!
ありがとっちでした！はい、お願いします！
Thank you so much! Okay, over to you!
はい、ということで社長？
Alright, so Boss?
あ、なんか、うん、今さっきからね
Ah, well, yeah, just now...
Xがトレンド2位だって！
We're trending #2 on X!
えー！すごい！すごい！
What?! Amazing! Amazing!
XってあのSNSですか？
Is X that social media platform?
やばい！あの有名な！
No way! That famous one!
それ以外ないだろ！
What else could it be?!
ね、たくさんポストしてくださってありがとうございます！引き続きよろしくお願いします！
Thank you all so much for posting! Please keep supporting us!
よろしくお願いします！
Please do!
いや、でも久しぶりにさ、『ラクガキMODE』と『SUPER DUPER』なんか歌ったね！しかも今回...
Man, but it's been a while since we sang 'LAKUGAKI MODE' and 'SUPER DUPER'! And this time...
こうなんていうの、ミックスバージョンみたいなさ
It was like... what do you call it, a mixed version!
『SUPER DUPER』は久しぶり...
'SUPER DUPER' was after a while...
まあでもさ、一応ね、一応一年経ったんで、一緒に歌っていただいたんですけど...
Well, since it's been a year, we sang it together...
そう、なんかちょっとね、久しぶりに聞けて嬉しくなっちゃったな！
Yeah, hearing it after so long made me so happy!
1年ぶり... 1年ぶりくらいか、確かに
1 year... About a year ago, true.
お披露目以来...
Since our debut reveal...
最後のポーズ何だったの？みんな
What was that final pose everyone did?
これは... 奏な！
This was... Kanade!
当ててほしい！コメントで！
We want you to guess in the comments!
はい！はい！
Yes! Yes!
何だったと思う？
What do you think it was?
社長のこれマジで何？
Boss, what was yours, seriously?
みんなで決めたやん！意味分からない！
We decided on it together! I don't get why you're asking!
あ、あ、これ分かった！
Ah, ah, I get this one!
これ分かる！これ何？
I get this one! What is this?
鳴き声は？ピュピュッ！
What sound does it make? Pyu pyu!
コケコッコーだろ！それはニワトリだよ！
That's a cock-a-doodle-doo! That's a chicken!
あ、でもヒヨコちゃん！ピヨピヨピヨ...
Ah, but a chick! Piyo piyo piyo...
番長のは？これ分かりやすいんじゃない？
What about Bancho's? Isn't this one easy to tell?
鳴き声は？ぴょんぴょん！
What sound does it make? Pyon pyon!
本当か？鳴くかな？あ、ペンギンって言ってる！
Really? Does it make a sound? Ah, someone said penguin!
おー！すごい！ってことはらでんちゃんも？
Ooh! Awesome! Then what about Raden-chan?
ニャ〜〜〜！
Meow~~~!
威嚇気味のねこちゃん！可愛いですね。
A feisty kitty! How cute.
はい、なんと最後はね、みんなでそれぞれの動物を表現しておりました！
Yes, at the end, we were all expressing our respective animals!
じゃあ、ちょっとここで一つ、嬉しいお知らせがあります！
Now, we have a piece of exciting news for you!
なんと！KONAMIさんとのコラボが決定しましたー！
Surprisingly, a collaboration with KONAMI has been confirmed!
書き下ろしのコラボ楽曲や、KONAMIオリジナル楽曲のカバーバージョンがBEMANI機種に登場します！
Original collaboration songs and cover versions of KONAMI originals will be added to BEMANI arcade games!
詳細はBEMANIファンサイトと公式Xをチェックしてください！
Please check the BEMANI Fan Site and official X for more details!
可愛い！可愛いね～
So cute! How cute~
色々ね、歌ったよね！コラボに関してさ
We sang various songs for this collaboration!
おしゃれでエモい感じの楽曲をね、ReGLOSSで歌わせていただいたんですよ！
We got to sing stylish and emotional songs as ReGLOSS!
ぜひプレイして聴いてみてほしいです！
We hope you play the games and listen to them!
なんかソロでもさ、ユニットとしても歌ったよね！
We sang both solo and as units!
なんかポジティブになれたね
I feel like we've gotten so positive.
うん、ほんとに
Yeah, really.
色々聴けると思うので、楽しみに待っていてくださーい！
You'll get to hear all kinds of things, so please look forward to it!
はーい！
Yay!
はい、皆さん息は大丈夫そうですか？
Alright, is everyone holding up okay with their breathing?
ですか？
Are you?
ギリ！
Barely!
ギリ？ もうちょっと喋る？ もうちょっと喋る？
Barely? Want to chat a bit more? Chat a bit more?
ギリ大丈夫、でも行けそう！
Barely okay, but we can do this!
はい！ということでね、じゃあみんなまだまだ...
Alright! So then, everyone, we're not...
まだまだ！ まだまだ終わりませんよ！ まだまだ何かあるかもしれないですよ！
Not yet! It's not over yet! There might still be something else coming!
はい！ ハッシュタグこれもお願いします！ 祝ってください！ #ReGLOSS2周年！
Yes! Please post using this hashtag too! Please celebrate with us! #ReGLOSS2ndAnniversary!
はい！ じゃあ次の曲、いいですかー？
Alright! Then for the next song, are you ready?
次の楽曲はなんと...
The next song is actually...
本日公開されたばかりの...あの曲！
that song that was just released today!
うわー！
Whoa~!
じゃあ、立ち位置につきますかー
Alright, shall we get into our positions?
はい！ なんの曲かなー？
Okay! What song could it be?
それでは聴いてください、『アワータイムイエロー』
Now then, please listen to "Hour Time Yellow".
ソラをボエで挑む人生ゲーム
Challenging the game of life by winging it,
言い訳めいたハートに従って
following a heart full of excuses.
現実は半即興なプロットです
Reality is a semi-improvised plot,
取り憑かれるオーバーな芝居
possessed by overly dramatic acting.
世渡り上手なあの子はね
That girl who's so good at navigating life, you see,
二度と被った猫外せない
can never take off that innocent mask again.
痛みを知ってしまった magician
A magician who has come to know pain
手の内は未だ明かせない
still cannot reveal their trick.
Yellow yellow ゼロからループ点滅するピリオド
Yellow, yellow, looping from zero, a blinking period.
Yellow yellow 染まる紅い化粧
Yellow, yellow, stained in crimson makeup.
I wonder if I can make it or not
例えツキに見放されても No worries 私には私がついてる
Even if luck abandons me, no worries, I've got myself.
宵が醒めるまであと少しだけ 真のアイ捉える残像
Just a little more until the night wears off, catching an afterimage of true love.
Slow and steady wins the race 次の季節を越え Blooming blooming
Slow and steady wins the race, crossing into the next season, blooming blooming.
どうかこの音を止めないで
Please don't stop this sound.
Hourtime yellow yellow Let it blow, let it blow ずっとの Stay gold
Hourtime yellow yellow, let it blow, let it blow, staying gold forever.
Hourtime yellow yellow Let it blow, let it blow Let's enjoy the moment
Look into the mirror 絡まってる蜘蛛の糸
Look into the mirror, caught in a spider's web.
It happens all the time 踊らされたって構わない
It happens all the time, I don't care if I'm made to dance.
夜を日に継いで 時を編んで明け暮れて
Working day and night, weaving time from dusk to dawn,
Always be honest 永遠に変わらないもの
Always be honest, things that never change.
Yellow yellow 手を取り合えばそこに理由は要らない
Yellow, yellow, if we hold hands, no reasons are needed.
Yellow yellow 染まる紅い化粧
Yellow, yellow, stained in crimson makeup.
A smile suits you best
幾つになっても Changeless 希望 夢は人知れず
No matter how old I get, changeless, hopes and dreams remain hidden.
歪で数奇な運命や 人生ごと受け入れる
Accepting distorted, eventful destiny and life as a whole.
心機一転 二転 三転 詠んで
A sudden turn of heart, two turns, three turns, reading the room,
第五感で Lock on
locking on with the fifth sense.
右見て左見て Pause 前だけ向いて Go on
Look right, look left, pause, face forward and go on.
歌い続ける 24/7
Continuing to sing 24/7.
終着地点は Eden or Heaven?
Is the final destination Eden or Heaven?
No time to waste "今"だけを信じてる
No time to waste, believing only in "now".
最後のフィナーレまで共に進め
Pressing forward together until the final finale.
宵が醒めるまであと少しだけ 真のアイ捉える残像
Just a little more until the night wears off, catching an afterimage of true love.
Slow and steady wins the race 次の季節を越え Blooming blooming
Slow and steady wins the race, crossing into the next season, blooming blooming.
どうかこの音を止めないで
Please don't stop this sound.
Hourtime yellow yellow Let it blow, let it blow ずっとの Stay gold
Hourtime yellow yellow, let it blow, let it blow, staying gold forever.
Hourtime yellow yellow Let it blow, let it blow Let's enjoy the moment
一振りのダンス、一瞬の視線、一拍の鼓動
[A stroke of dance, a momentary glance, a single beat of heart]
一秒一秒が永遠に鳴り響く
[Every single second echoes into eternity]
ReGLOSSが描いていく“今”を切り取った一枚一枚の連続
[A series of moments capturing the "now" drawn by ReGLOSS]
そのすべてが連なり 観る人の記憶に焼きついていく
[Connecting them all to burn into the memories of those who watch]
2025.12.16 Tue. Flashpoint ReGLOSS 1st Live
ARIAKE ARENA
それぞれの光が響き合い、世界をかたちづくる
[Their respective lights resonate together, shaping the world]
ReGLOSSはその瞬間を音楽とダンスで伝える
[ReGLOSS conveys that moment through music and dance]
はーい！
Yay!
ということで！みんな見た？見た？見た？
So, did everyone see it? Did you see it?
やばい！
Oh my gosh!
12月16日、有明アリーナ...
On December 16th, at Ariake Ari...
もう一回！テイク2、テイク2、テイク2！
One more time! Take 2, Take 2, Take 2!
もう一回行こう！うん！12月16日、有明アリーナにて！
Let me try again! Yep! On December 16th, at Ariake Arena!
ReGLOSS 1st Live『Flashpoint』の開催が決定いたしましたー！
ReGLOSS 1st Live "Flashpoint" has been announced!
やったー！
Yay!
すごい！すごい！すごい！
Amazing! Amazing! Amazing!
え、現地ライブってことだよね？そうだよ！
Wait, does that mean an in-person concert? Yes, it is!
しかもめちゃくちゃでかい会場だよ！そうだよね！
And it's at a huge venue! Right?!
やばい！夢が叶うってこと？！
Oh my gosh! Does this mean our dream is coming true?!
みんな、ありがとう！応援してくれたみんなのおかげだね！
Thank you, everyone! It's all thanks to everyone who supported us!
1個目の夢が叶うかもしれないんだ！頑張ろう！
One of our dreams might come true! Let's do our best!
はい！で、こちらのライブなんですけれども、2ndアルバムで描いた世界観に連動して、ReGLOSSの「今」を記憶に焼き付ける、というテーマになっています！
Yes! As for this concert, in line with the world described in our 2nd album, the theme is to engrave the "present" of ReGLOSS into your memories!
つまり！まさに今の私たちの集大成となるライブでございます！
In other words! It's a concert that serves as the culmination of who we are right now!
イエーイ！で、ちょっとね、ライブのキービジュアルも改めてお見せしちゃいたい...
Yay! And we'd like to show you the key visual for the concert again...
こちら！デデン！うわー！かっこいい！ねー！
Here it is! Ta-da! Whoa! So cool! Right?!
こちらのキービジュアルはね、ライブのテーマに合わせてライブパフォーマンス中のReGLOSSを切り取ったイメージのデザインとなっています！
This key visual is designed around the theme of the concert, capturing ReGLOSS mid-performance!
へぇ〜！ステキ！なんかまた普段のReGLOSSとは違った一面な感じがしたね！
Whoa! Lovely! It feels like showing a different side of ReGLOSS than usual!
今回のライブのハッシュタグは #ReGLOSS_1stLive です！いっぱいポストして皆で盛り上がりましょう！
The hashtag for this concert is #ReGLOSS_1stLive! Please post a lot so we can all get excited together!
お願いします！
Please do!
さて、そんな中、皆さんが気になっているであろうチケット情報を皆さんにお見せしようかなと思います！チケット情報はこちら！デデン！
Now then, we'd like to share the ticket information that you're probably all curious about! Here's the ticket info! Ta-da!
はい！チケットはS席、A席、B席の3種類です！
Yes! There are 3 types of tickets: S seats, A seats, and B seats!
1次先行はこのあと21時からスタートです！
The 1st pre-order sales start tonight at 21:00!
先着ではございません！抽選でございます！焦らずにお申し込みください！
It's not first-come, first-served! It's a lottery! Please apply without rushing!
さらに「会場には行けないよ〜」という人のために配信チケットもご用意しました！
Furthermore, for those who can't make it to the venue, we also prepared streaming tickets!
こちらもこのあと21時から販売開始です！
These will also go on sale tonight at 21:00!
続いて、会場のエリアマップはこちら！ジャン！
Next, here is the venue seat map! Ta-da!
S席、A席、B席がそれぞれどこになるのかはこちらをチェックしてください！
Please check here to see where S, A, and B seats are located!
エリアマップはこのあとホロライブ公式Xでもポストするので、詳しくはそちらをご確認ください！そしてみんな、喜べ！トレンド1位！
The seat map will also be posted on the official Hololive X account later, so check there for details! And everyone, rejoice! We're #1 on trending!
やったー！嬉しい！ありがとう！
Yay! So happy! Thank you!
ありがとう！2周年も祝ってくれて嬉しいな！ねー！
Thank you! We're so glad you're celebrating our 2nd anniversary with us too! Right?!
そしてそして！ライブのグッズについては10月10日のReGLOSSの公式配信で発表します！
And also! Details about concert merchandise will be announced during the official ReGLOSS stream on October 10th!
楽しみ！素敵なグッズがいっぱいあるので見逃さないでね！
Can't wait! There are lots of wonderful merch items, so don't miss out!
そしてそして！今回発表したライブの情報や次回のグッズの情報は特設サイトにて掲載いたします！
And also! The concert information announced today and future merch details will be posted on the special website!
特設サイト...あ、うちら事前に行ったよね！言ってたかも！
The special website... Ah, we talked about it beforehand! We might have mentioned it!
はい！すごくかっこいいサイトなんで、ぜひとも覗いてみてください！
Yes! It's a super cool site, so please be sure to check it out!
特設サイトは「ReGLOSS 1st Live」で検索をお願いします！
Search "ReGLOSS 1st Live" to find the special website!
今後も追加情報を更新していくので、ブックマークとチェックをよろしくお願いします！
We will keep updating with more info, so please bookmark and check back often!
現地ですってよ！やばいね！どうよ、みんな？
They said it's an in-person concert! That's crazy! How are you all feeling?
はい！莉々華はデビューの時から言ってるんだけど、ダンスも歌も自信がなかったし、得意じゃないって思ってた莉々華が...
Yes! Ririka has been saying this since debut, but I wasn't confident in dancing or singing, and thought I wasn't good at it...
ちょっとずつそれぞれを好きになっていけていて、みんなにちゃんと成長した姿を見てもらいたいって思ってて...
...but step by step, I've come to enjoy them, and I really want everyone to see how much I've grown...
その夢が新しい現地ライブっていう場で叶うのかもしれないって思ったらめちゃくちゃ嬉しいです！
...and thinking that dream might come true at this new live event makes me so incredibly happy!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
と...
Um...
え、奏は
Kanade...
なんか正直まだ実感が湧いてなくって
honestly still hasn't fully registered it yet,
現地ライブ...
a live venue show...
本当に... 本当に...みたいな
Like, 'Really...? Really...?'
なんか実感が本当に湧かなくて...
It really hasn't sunk in...
でもなんか、ずっとさ現地ライブしたい、したいって言ってきて、いざ決定！ってなって
But we kept saying we wanted a live venue show, and when it was finally decided...
世に出て、なんか本当に不思議な気持ち
and announced to the world, it felt so surreal.
めちゃくちゃ嬉しいんだけどね！
I'm super happy, though!
なんか夢のようで、なんか逆に何も感じないような...
It feels like a dream, so in a way, it's hard to process...
じわじわ後から、うわー！嬉しい！ってなると思うんだけど...
I think it'll gradually hit me later, like 'Whoa, I'm so happy!'...
おめでとう！ありがとう！
Congratulations! Thank you!
みんなのおかげです！
It's all thanks to everyone!
番長はどう？
How about you, Bancho?
いや、同じくね、実感が湧かなくて...
Yeah, same here, it hasn't quite set in...
本当なんだろ、夢見心地でよく分からないけど
It really feels like a dream, so I don't fully get it yet, but...
でも、もうあと3ヶ月くらいしたら...
in about 3 months, though...
ReGLOSSのみんなが目の前にいて...
everyone in ReGLOSS will be right in front of us...
パフォーマンス...
performing...
みんなが目の前にいて「キャー！」ってやって来られるってことでしょ？
and everyone will be right there cheering 'Yay!' right?
ってやって来られちゃうと思ったら...
Thinking about everyone coming to see us...
もうすっごい嬉しいですし、本当にありがとうございます！
makes me so happy, thank you all so much!
嬉しいね！そしてらでんちゃんは？
That's wonderful! And how about Raden-chan?
はい！現地ライブということで、12月少し早めのReGLOSSからのクリスマスプレゼントということで...
Yes! A live venue show, like an early Christmas gift from ReGLOSS in December...
現地ライブさせていただくんですけれども...
We get to perform a live venue show, but...
まさかね、まさかまさかの現地ライブで...
Never in a million years did I expect a live venue show...
本当にこんなありがたい機会がいただけるって、生きててなかなか無いじゃない？
To get such a wonderful opportunity is a rare thing in life, right?
無いよ！無いよ！
It really is!
そう！だからすごくありがたいなと思うし、嬉しいなと思いますし...
Right! So I feel so grateful and happy about it...
今ね、絶賛こうレッスンでね...
And right now, we're in the middle of lessons...
ライブに向けて我々頑張っておりますので...
We're practicing hard for the live show...
ぜひ今後も応援してくれるととっても嬉しいです！
so we'd be thrilled if you keep supporting us!
皆さん本当にありがとうございます！
Thank you all so much!
ありがとうございますー！
Thank you so much!
ねー、いやー本当ライブ嬉しいね！
Yeah, I'm really so happy about the live show!
最高だね！
It's the best!
でもその、ライブのためってわけでもないけどさ、いろんな楽曲を歌わせていただいていて...
Not just for the live show, but we've gotten to sing various songs...
今回「Our Time Yellow」もね、新しくリリースさせていただいたわけなんですけれども...
and we recently released 'Our Time Yellow' as well...
ちょっとその感想も話しちゃおうか、ここでね！「Our Time Yellow」のね！
Let's share our thoughts on 'Our Time Yellow' right here!
じゃあ逆順で行く？らでんちゃんどう？
Shall we go in reverse order? How about you, Raden-chan?
あ！らでんはね、MV出たじゃん？
Ah, for Raden, the MV came out, right?
MV出たから、いろんなものが素敵なんだけど、中でもらでんは歌詞がすっごい好きで...
Everything in the MV is wonderful, but I especially love the lyrics...
ちょっとMV見て「あ、良い曲だな」とか「MVめちゃめちゃ動いていいな」と思った方は...
If you watched the MV and thought 'Oh, what a great song' or 'The animation is so active'...
もう一回次は歌詞に注目してくれるとすごく嬉しいな、なんて思います！
I'd be so happy if you focus on the lyrics next time!
番長は？
How about Bancho?
いや、もうとにかくリズムとメロディが好きでしてね！
I just love the rhythm and melody so much!
ずっとやってる！
You've been doing that motion non-stop!
疾走感があって...
It has such a sense of speed...
乗ってる言葉のメロディも全部リズム良かったり、チュウンチュウンって言ったり...
The melody of the words fits the rhythm so well, with cool dynamic sounds...
激しいやん、移り変わりが！飽きの来ない展開というかさ！
The transitions are so intense, it never gets boring!
なんかもうすごいメロディ大好きっす！
I just really love the melody!
ぜひ聴いてください！
Please give it a listen!
奏はまず曲がものすごく大好きだし...
Kanade loves the song so much first of all...
今日みんなとさ、初めてMVを見たじゃないですか！
And today, we all watched the MV together for the first time, right?
MVを見ると、なんかすごいかっこいい感じになっていて、大感激でした！
Seeing the MV, it looked so cool, I was deeply moved!
個人的に奏が一番好きなMVシーンは...
Personally, my favorite scene in the MV is...
こう... こういうシーン！
This... this kind of scene!
1番の終わりの... サビの終わりのところ！
At the end of the first chorus!
あー、あそこのプリョンってやつ？
Ah, that 'swish' movement part?
この日のためにシャンプー頑張りました！
I washed my hair thoroughly with shampoo for this day!
サラサー！
Silky smooth!
リリカは？
How about Lirika?
いや、リリカもね、やっぱり「Our Time Yellow」はすごく元気になれる曲じゃない？
Well, 'Our Time Yellow' is such an energizing song, right?
テンションアゲアゲってなる曲で、聞いてて楽しいし...
It really pumps you up and is so fun to listen to...
あと踊ってても、激しいところが大好きです！
and even while dancing, I love all the intense moves!
たぶんそんなに失敗しなかったです！
I don't think I made many mistakes!
見てください！聴いてください！
Please watch it and listen to it!
え、このサビのさ、これめっちゃかっこよくない？
Hey, isn't this part in the chorus super cool?
ここ！ここ好きなんだけど！
Here! I love this part!
あー、分かる！
Ah, I totally get it!
こっち！こっち！こっち！
This move! This one! This one!
分かる、分かる！
I know, right?
まあね、引き続き私たちはアルバムに収録される新曲の練習なんかもね、めちゃくちゃ頑張ってますので...
Well, we're continuing to practice hard for the new songs on our album as well...
ライブ楽しみにしていてくれたら嬉しいです！
so we hope you look forward to the live concert!
それじゃあ最後の曲行きますか！
Well then, shall we move on to the final song?
最後ですか...
The last song already...
行ける？
Ready?
お水飲んどく？
Want to drink some water?
何の曲かな？
What song could it be?
みんな何の曲だと思う？
What song do you all think it is?
何歌おうかな？
What should I sing?
ReGLOSSの曲だったら... やっぱ最後は「瞬感ハートベイト」じゃない？
If it's a ReGLOSS song... Shouldn't the last one be "Shunkan Heartbeat"?
「シンメトリー」とかじゃない？
Wouldn't it be "Symmetry"?
「Feeling Gradation」とかもあるしね。
There's also "Feeling Gradation".
うち水飲んでくるわ。
I'm gonna go drink some water.
いってらっしゃい。
Off you go!
元気だね。現地もそうだし、配信組も出てましたしね。
She's lively. Both at the venue and on the stream, people are excited!
立ち位置付きましたか？
Are you in position?
付きますか。付きましょうか。
In position? Shall we get in position?
あれ？ こっちということは？
Wait, being over here means...?
分かった人たぶんあんまりいないかもしれない。
There probably aren't many people who would figure it out.
うちらだけだと... あ、そうか。
If it's just us... Oh, I see!
立ち位置がここ... ということは... みたいな。
"Our standing positions are here, which means..." like that.
はい、それでは、聴いてください、「ミッドサマーシトラス」。
Alright then, please listen to "Midsummer Citrus".
今日は2周年だから...
Today is our 2nd anniversary, so...
手を沈静化...
...calm your hands down!
負けない！
I won't lose!
灼けつくような日差し
Scorching sunlight,
水面に浮かぶスパンコール
Sequins floating on the water's surface.
燥ぐ夏色と逆光の裏側で
Behind the playful summer colors and backlighting,
あの日の青春を呼び起こしてる
It awakens the youth of those days.
デニムの裾を捲って
Rolling up the hems of my denim,
裸足で走ってる砂の上
Running barefoot over the sand.
硝子の淵で回り回る
Spinning around on the edge of the glass,
輝く瑠璃色のビー玉
A shining, lapis lazuli marble.
なんだか、その笑顔と紙一重だ
Somehow, it's paper-thin close to that smile.
フィルムを覗けばノンフィクション
Peering through the film, it's non-fiction,
彩りに絆されたメモリー
Memories bound by colors.
リセットなんて出来ないから
Because we can't just reset them...
love yourself just as you are now
踊ってミッドサマー アルゴリズムの中 (ooh)
Dance, midsummer, inside the algorithm (ooh)
瞬息でダビングして 切り取って喜怒哀楽
Dubbing in an instant, cutting out all the emotions
これがきっと愛だ (ooh)
This must surely be love (ooh)
二度と忘れないように
So that we'll never forget it again
(oh) le lemon lime orange キミといっしょ分の思い出
(oh) le lemon lime orange, a lifetime's worth of memories with you
(oh) 何気ない一日が one of a kind
(oh) A casual day becomes one of a kind
氷が溶けては渦巻いた
As the ice melts, it swirls,
魔法の杖がわりのマドラー
A stirrer acting as a magic wand.
喉の奥くすぐる炭酸
Carbonation tickling the back of the throat,
香る柑橘系のフレイバー
A fragrant citrus flavor.
爽やかな気流にのって
Riding on a refreshing air current,
波の還りを見守ってる beachside
Watching over the return of the waves on the beachside.
あどけない面影に焦がれ
Longing for an innocent visage,
微かに触れそうな指先
Fingertips that feel like they could faintly touch.
煌めきで上塗りしてしまおう
Let's paint over it with sparkle,
get ahead of what you used to be
踊ってミッドサマー アルゴリズムの中 (ooh)
Dance, midsummer, inside the algorithm (ooh)
瞬息でダビングして 切り取って喜怒哀楽
Dubbing in an instant, cutting out all the emotions
これがきっと愛だ (ooh)
This must surely be love (ooh)
二度と忘れないように
So that we'll never forget it again
ミッドサマーシトラス oh yeah
Midsummer citrus, oh yeah
いつだって we got love !! okay
Whenever, we got love !! okay
キミがいるだけで feel so nice ココロはまた実り
Just being with you feels so nice, my heart bears fruit again
寝起きの太陽も 願ってもない燦々日和？
Even the morning sun is an unexpectedly bright day?
白飛びしてしまうほど 眩しいのは夏のせい
It's summer's fault that it's so dazzling it overexposes
踊ってミッドサマー アルゴリズムの中 (ooh)
Dance, midsummer, inside the algorithm (ooh)
瞬息でダビングして 切り取って喜怒哀楽
Dubbing in an instant, cutting out all the emotions
これがきっと愛だ (ooh)
This must surely be love (ooh)
二度と忘れないように
So that we'll never forget it again
(oh) le lemon lime orange キミといっしょ分の思い出
(oh) le lemon lime orange, a lifetime's worth of memories with you
(oh) 何気ない一日が one of a kind
(oh) A casual day becomes one of a kind
ありがとうございました！
Thank you so much!
12月16日、みんなと会えるの楽しみにしているよ！
Looking forward to meeting everyone on December 16th!
有明アリーナも配信も、全力で盛り上げます！
We'll bring full energy to both Ariake Arena and the stream!
これからもお楽しみに！
Please look forward to what's coming!
1stアルバムもたくさん聴いてください！
Please listen to our 1st album a lot too!
ということで、せーの、ReGLOSSでした！
And with that, ready... We were ReGLOSS!
現地でお会いしましょう！
See you at the venue!